<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LeetCode on Jingxi&#39;s personal blog.</title>
    <link>https://misscherylwang.github.io/tags/leetcode/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LeetCode on Jingxi&#39;s personal blog.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:25:22 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://misscherylwang.github.io/tags/leetcode/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>973.K Closest Points to Origin-与原点最近的K个点</title>
      <link>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/lc973/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:25:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/lc973/</guid>
      <description>问题描述 We have a list of points on the plane. Find the K closest points to the origin (0, 0). (Here, the distance between two points on a plane is the Euclidean distance.) You may return the answer in any order. The answer is guaranteed to be unique (except for the order that it is in.) Example: Input: points = [[3,3],[5,-1],[-2,4]], K = 1 Output: [[3,3]] 问</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1483. Kth Ancestor of a Tree Node-一个树结点的第K个祖先</title>
      <link>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/lc1483/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 23:46:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/lc1483/</guid>
      <description>问题说明 You are given a tree with n nodes numbered from 0 to n-1 in the form of a parent array where parent[i] is the parent of node i. The root of the tree is node 0. Implement the function getKthAncestor(int node, int k) to return the k-th ancestor of the given node. If there is no such ancestor, return -1. The k-th ancestor of a tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1482. Minimum Number of Days to Make m Bouquets-制造M束花束需要的最少天数</title>
      <link>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode1482/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 01:00:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode1482/</guid>
      <description>问题说明 Given an integer array bloomDay, an integer m and an integer k. We need to make m bouquets. To make a bouquet, you need to use k adjacent flowers from the garden. The garden consists of n flowers, the ith flower will bloom in the bloomDay[i] and then can be used in exactly one bouquet. Return the minimum number of days you need to wait to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1277. Count Square Submatrices with All Ones-数出所有的全1方阵</title>
      <link>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode1277/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 17:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode1277/</guid>
      <description>问题描述 Given a m * n matrix of ones and zeros, return how many square submatrices have all ones. Example: Input: matrix = [ [0,1,1,1], [1,1,1,1], [0,1,1,1] ] Output: 15 从上面的栗子可以看出方形子矩阵边为1的有10个，边为2的有4个，边为3的有</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1481. Least Number of Unique Integers after K Removals-K清除后的不同元素的最小个数</title>
      <link>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode1481/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 18:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode1481/</guid>
      <description>问题描述 Given an array of integers arr and an integer k. Find the least number of unique integers after removing exactly k elements. Example: Input: arr = [5,5,4], k = 1 Output: 1 解题思路 这道题目求解在数组中去除k个元素后所剩余的不同元素的最小值。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>813. Largest Sum of Averages-最大的平均数之和</title>
      <link>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode813/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 17:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://misscherylwang.github.io/post/leetcode813/</guid>
      <description>问题描述 We partition a row of numbers A into at most K adjacent (non-empty) groups, then our score is the sum of the average of each group. What is the largest score we can achieve? Note that our partition must use every number in A, and that scores are not necessarily integers. Example: Input: A = [9,1,2,3,9] K = 3 Output: 20 这道题目求</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>